U.S. National Mediation Board Agreements 5806
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. National Mediation Board Agreements
1921-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. National Mediation Board
5806
85 cubic feet
85 linear ft.
Agreements.
3126347
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 25, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 10, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; United States. National Mediation Board
3126347
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1926-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers - Agreement, Elgin, Joliet Southern Railway Co., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The New York Central Railway Company, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Kansas Southern Railway Company, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company, The States Island Railroad Corporation, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Misc. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific railroad Company (Lines East), 1924-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Baltimore and Hudson Railway Company, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- National Railroad Adjustment Board - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co. - UTU, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Agreements (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Santa Maia Valley Railroad and B.L.E., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Texas Mexican Railway Company - UTU, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Grand Trunk Western Railway Co. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Between the Southern Pacific Transportation Company (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company (Box 1, Folder 18)
- The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company (Box 1, Folder 19)
- South Pacific Transportation Company (Box 1, Folder 20)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1927-1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- NULL (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company, 1927-1953 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Lake Erie Railroad Company - UTU, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Pacific Railroad Company - BLE, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- The Western Pacific Railroad Company - UTU, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Missouri- Kansas- Texas Railroad Company, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Union Railroad Company - UTU, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- The Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Seaboard Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 2, Folder 10)
- New Orleans Public Belt Railroad - UTU, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Union Railroad Company - BLE, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1925-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Railroad Companies, 1924-1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Norfolk Railway Companies, 1924-1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Union Pacific Railroad Co., 1923-1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railway, Other Railways, 1925-1957 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Agreement, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Kansas City Southern Railway and Louisville Nashville Railroad Company, 1927-1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Minneapolis, St. Paul Railroad Company - B.L.F.E., 1924-1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- (New England Area) Railroad Companies, 1940-1957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Minneapolis, South Omaha, St. Louis Railway Companies, 1925-1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Southern Pacific Lines and Southern Railway Companies, 1929-1955 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Western Pacific and Illinois Ventral Railroad Company, 1924-1941 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Erie Railroad Company and Illinois Central Railroad Company, 1920-1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- The Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company, 1923- 1937 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Minneapolis and Missouri Railroad Companies, 1924-1958 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company, 1940-1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Illinois Railway and Railroad Companies, 1928-1954 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- DM IR Railway Company - Missabe Division Enginemen (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Chicago Yazoo Mississippi Valley Railway Companies, 1924-1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Denver and Western Maryland Railway Companies, 1935-1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Northern and Southern Railway, 1925-1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Texas Railroad Companies, 1925-1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company and Atchison, Topeka, Sana Fe Railway Company, 1931-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- New York Central Railroad and Baltimore- Ohio Railway Company, 1924-1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company, 1936-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company and Denver, Rio Grande, 1927-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Missouri Pacific, Atlantic Coast Line, Maine Central Railroad Companies, 1924-1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Chicago and Delaware Railway Companies, 1922-1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Chicago and Eastern Illinois, Colorado and Santa Fe, Portland Terminal Railway Companies, 1922-1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Missouri Pacific, Texas and Pacific, Louisville and Nashville Railway Company, 1927-1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Illinois, Michigan Railway Companies, 1928-1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- The Belt Railway Company of Chicago, 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Company, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- San Antonio Joint Car Interchange Association, 1949-1953 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- San Diego and Arizona Eastern Railway Company, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Savannah Union Station Company, 1942-1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Seaboard Airline Railway Railroad Companies, 1939-1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Seaboard Coastline Railroad Company, 1943-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Soo Line Railroad Company, 1949-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Southern Pacific Company, 1949-1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- National Carriers' Conference Committee, 1951-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- The Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- The Kansas City Southern Railway Committee, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Clinchfield Railroad Company, 1949-1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Railroad Passenger Association, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company, 1940-1957 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company, 1939-1957 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Southern Railway et al. and Int'l Association of Machinists, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie and the Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad Companies, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Company, 1941-1957 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie and the Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad Companies, 1952-1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Southern Pacific, 1943-1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Southern Pacific, 1937-1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- The Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Peoria and Pekin Union Railway Company, 1946-1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Denver and Rio Railway Company, 1924-1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Chicago and North Western Railway Company, 1907-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Union Pacific, Colorado Railway Companies, 1923-1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Western Pacific, Northern Pacific Railway Companies, 1921-1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- New Orleans, Western Maryland and Southern Pacific Railway Companies, 1924-1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Kansas City, Chicago Railway Companies, 1924-1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe, Lehigh Valley Railway Companies, 1923-1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Chesapeake, Ohio, Wabash Railway Companies, 1922-1936 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Detroit and Toledo, Missouri-Illinois Railway Companies, 1928-1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Union Railway Company and Boston Albany Railroad, 1924-1947 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Chicago Railroad Companies, 1924-1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1927-1960 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1927-1960 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Denver and Rio Grande- Central of Georgia Railway, 1927-1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1918-1951 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1928-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1919-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Atchison, Topeka, Santa Fe, Railway Company, 1924-1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Atchison, Topeka, Santa Fe, Railway Company, 1940-1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1939-1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Northern Pacific and Colorado Railroad Companies, 1920-1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Norfolk Railroad Companies, 1927-1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1927-1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Northern Pacific and Southern Pacific Railway, 1925-1957 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- New York Central Railway, 1924-1955 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Boston Railroads and Reading Company, 1924-1938 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Southern Railway Companies, 1920-1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Maine and Michigan Central Raiload Company, 1930-1947 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Georgia Railroad Companies and Missouri Pacific, 1924-1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Great Northern Norfolk and Western Railway Companies, 1927-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Union Pacific Railway Company, 1939-1958 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Illinois Central amp; St. Louis San Francisco and Jacksonville Railway Companies, 1919-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Southern Pacific Railroad Company, 1928-1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1924-1958 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Kansas City Southern Ogden Railway Company, 1921-1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Western Maryland and Oregon Short Line Railroad Companies, 1925-1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Pacific Electric Railway Company- Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company, 1927-1959 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Nickel Plate Road Chicago Great Western Railroad Company, 1924-1958 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- New York Central Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Companies, 1927-1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1943-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- New York Central Railroad- Nickel Plate Railroad, 1924-1953 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Northern Pacific Railway Company, 1910-1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Oregon Short Line- Ogden Union Railway and Depot Company, 1931-1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Nickel Plate Road, Rio Grande, Southern Railroad Companies, 1924-1953 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Southern Pacific Company St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company, 1931-1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Western Maryland Railway and Southern Pacific Railway Company, 1919-1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Reading Company and Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1926-1955 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Western Pacific Railroad - New Orleans Terminal Company, 1922-1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- St. Louis, Minneapolis Railway Companies, 1910-1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Southern Pacific and Pacific Electric Railway Companies, 1942-1953 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Minneapolis, St. Paul amp; Sault Ste. Marie Railroad, 1924-1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Fort Worth Belt Railway, The Virginian Railway Company, and The Railroad Company, 1912-1955 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Northern Pacific and Illinois Terminal Railroad Company, 1912-1948 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- The Virginia Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 1)
- The Virginia Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 2)
- The Virginia Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Wabash Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Western Pacific Railroad Company (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Youngstown and Southern Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Tennessee Central Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Wheeling and Lake Erie Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Terminal Railroad Association (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis (Box 10, Folder 10)
- The Texas and Pacific Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Toledo Lakefront Dock Company (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Toledo Peoria and Western Railroad Co. (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Tulsa Union Depot Company (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Union Belt, Terminal and Railway Companies (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Toledo, Peoria Western Railroad Co. (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Southern Railway and Sheet Meal Workers International Association (Box 10, Folder 17)
- South Buffalo Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railway Company (Box 10, Folder 19)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Southern Railway and International Association of Machinists (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Chicago and North Western Transportation Company (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Northeast Illinois Regional Commuter Railroad Corporation ( A Public Corporation) (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Richmond Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Southern Railway and Sheet Metal Workers International Association (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Pacific Electric Railway Company, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Pacific Fruit Express Company, 1945-1950 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1941-1955 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania- Reading Seashore Lines, 1941-1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Peoria and Pekin Union Railway Company, 1946-1958 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Patapsco and Back Rives Railroad Company, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Piedmont and Northern Railway Company Co., 1942-1968 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company, 1948-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company, 1955-1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Companies, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- The Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway Company, 1945-1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company, 1939-1957 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company, 1939-1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Sacramento Northern Railway Co., 1937-1946 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Company, 1950-1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Company, 1945-1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Company, 1945-1975 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Company, 1949-1953 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company, 1953-1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- The New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1944-1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Niagara Junction Railway Company, 1948-1955 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1939-1964 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Northern Pacific Railway Company, 1945-1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Northwestern Pacific Railroad Company, 1937-1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Dispatch Shops, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Michigan Central Railroad Company, 1935-1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1949-1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- New Orleans Public Belt Railroad, 1967-1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1929-1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- New Jersey Transit Rail Operations, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Employees' National Conference Committee, 1955-1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Newburgh and South Shore Railroad Company, 1948-1970 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Mystic Terminal Company, 1939-1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company, 1939-1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company, 1947-1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company, 1933-1975 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Grand Trunk Western Railway Company, 1947-1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Great Northern Railway Company, 1946-1953 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Gulf Coast Lines, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Green Bay and Western Railroad Company, 1943-1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company, 1946-1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Illinois Central Terminal Railroad Companies, 1948-1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company, 1939-1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- International- Great Northern Railway Company, 1949-1953 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad Company Jacksonville Terminal Railroad Company, 1956-1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- The Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1944-1958 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Kansas City Terminal Railway Company, 1936-1949 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Kentucky and Indiana Terminal The Lakefront Dock and Railroad Terminal Company, 1948-1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Lake Erie, Franklin and Clarion Railroad Company, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Lake Superior Railroad Companies, 1944-1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- The Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1949-1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Missouri Railroad Companies, 1940-1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Lakefront Railroad Companies, 1921-1954 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- The Lake Terminal Railroad Company, 1955-1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad Company, 1944-1949 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Los Angeles Junction Railway Company Louisville Louisiana Railway Companies, 1931-1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Maine Central Railroad, McCloud River Railroad Company, 1937-1982 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Long Island Railroad Company, 1949-1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Maine Central Railroad Company, 1955-1976 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Portland Terminal Railway Company, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Minneapolis St. Paul and St. Marie Railway Company, 1943-1955 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Missouri Minnesota Railway Companies, 1935-1953 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Memphis Union State Company, 1936-1960 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- McKeesport Connecting Railroad, Manufacturers Railway Companies, 1967-1972 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Harbor Belt Houston Belt Railroad, 1939-1967 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Clinchfield Railroad Company, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Des Moines Central Iowa Railway Company, 1949-1965 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Duluth, Missabe, and Iron Range Railway Company, 1936-1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway Company, 1936-1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Erie Railroad System Lines, 1939-1951 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- The Cincinnati Union Terminal Company, 1943-1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Cleveland, Chicago, Cincinnati and St. Louis Railway, 1941-1955 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- The Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1922-1934 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Cleveland Union Terminals, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- The Colorado and Wyoming Railway Company, 1941-1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Columbus and Greenville Railway Company, 1942-1949 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railway Company, 1945-1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company, 1940-1949 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company, 1935-1952 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Chicago, Saint Paul, Minneapolis and Omaha Railway Company, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Chicago River and Indiana Railroad, 1943-1948 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Chicago Union Station Company, 1945-1959 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Chicago, West Pullman and Southern Railroad Company, 1952-1962 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Chicago South Shore and South Beach Railroad, 1952-1964 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Delray Connecting Railroad Company, 1962-1978 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Central Railway Companies, 1939-1957 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Charleston and Western Carolina Railway Company, 1929-1949 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1949-1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Chicago and Eastern Illinois Chicago and Midland Illinois Railway Companies, 1923-1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Chicago and Western Indiana Railway Companies, 1944-1966 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Chicago, Burlington ad Quincy Railroad Company, 1942-1966 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Misc. Chicago Railway Companies, 1944-1956 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Birmingham Southern Railroad Company, 1954-1976 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Burlington Northern Inc., 1923-1979 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Misc. Railroad Companies, 1923-1948 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway Company, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Alabama, Tennessee, and Northern Railway Company (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Aliquippa and Southern Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 2)
- The Alton and Southern Railroad (Box 15, Folder 3)
- American Refrigerator Transit Company and it's Employees (Box 15, Folder 4)
- The Ann Arbor Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Ashley, Drew and northern Railway Company (Box 15, Folder 6)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Bangor and Aroostook Railway Company (Box 15, Folder 9)
- The Belt Railway Company of Chicago (Box 15, Folder 10)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Atlanta Terminal Railway Company (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 13)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Auto-Train Corporation (Box 15, Folder 15)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Chicago Terminal Railroad (Box 15, Folder 16)
- The Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 17)
- The Belt Railway Company of Chicago (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Florida East Coast Railway Company (Box 15, Folder 19)
- New York Central Railroad (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Pittsburgh Railroad Companies (Box 15, Folder 21)
- The Denver and Salt Lake Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Besemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 23)
- National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Box 15, Folder 24)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company The Western, Pacific Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 25)
- The Texas and Pacific Railway Company, Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Des Moines and Central Iowa Railroad Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railroad Company (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company Kansas City Southern Lines (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Minneapolis Seaboard Air Line (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Texas Mexican Railway Northwestern Pacific Railroad Southern Railway Companies (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Southern Pacific Lines in Texas and Louisiana Richmond Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Reading Company Railway Express Agency (Box 16, Folder 4)
- St. Louis- San Francisco Railway Company (Box 16, Folder 5)
- The New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company- The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Portland Terminal Railroad Company Southern Railway Northern Railway Companies (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Boston and Albany Railroad The Pullman Company (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 16, Folder 9)
- New York Railroad Companies (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Burlington Northern Railroad Company (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company Southern Pacific Company (Box 16, Folder 12)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company The Pittsburgh and West Virginia Railway Company (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Kansas + Colorado Southern Railway Companies (Box 16, Folder 14)
- The Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railway The Monongahela Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 1)
- The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Southern Pacific Railroad New Orlenes and Lower Coast Railroad Companies (Box 17, Folder 3)